=The Glamorous Night=
=迷人的夜晚=
(Two years ago) Judging from your resume,
（两年前）从你的简历来看，
you have fairly extensive work experience.
你有相当丰富的工作经验。
But could you tell me
但你能告诉我吗
why you left your last company this March?
为什么你今年三月离开了上一家公司？
I'd rather not say.
我宁愿不说。
Then can you talk about your understanding of promotions?
那您能谈谈您对促销的理解吗？
Promotions?
促销活动？
Just promotions.
只是促销活动。
So why did you apply for this position at our company?
那么您为什么应聘我们公司的这个职位呢？
The pay is good.
薪水不错。
Can you tell me about your career plans and goals?
你能告诉我你的职业规划和目标吗？
I don't know.
我不知道。
Wang Hao.
Wang Hao.
You are Wang Hao, right?
你是王浩吧？
Yeah.
是的。
Do you have time now?
你现在有时间吗？
I do have time. What do you need?
我确实有时间。你需要什么？
Come on, have a coffee with me.
来吧，和我一起喝杯咖啡吧。
The coffee at this restaurant is just average. I'm not interested in it.
这家餐厅的咖啡很一般。我对此不感兴趣。
I think it's quite good.
我觉得还不错。
Just tell me,
只要告诉我，
why invited me for coffee?
为什么邀请我喝咖啡？
I looked at the case you sent earlier.
我看了你之前发来的案例。
I liked it. So I asked you to come for the interview.
我喜欢它。所以我邀请你来面试。
I meet you in person today. I think you are good.
今天我亲自见到你。我觉得你很好。
Very genuine and honest.
非常真诚和诚实。
I like that.
我喜欢这样。
But during the interview just now,
但在刚才的采访中，
I said things you didn't want to hear.
我说了你不想听的话。
No goals?
没有目标？
That's perfectly normal.
这是完全正常的。
I get confused too.
我也很困惑。
Even now, sometimes I don't know
即使现在，有时我也不知道
what my goals really are.
我的真正目标是什么。
Life just comes in stages.
人生只是阶段性的。
You can find a job to do for now.
你现在可以找一份工作来做。
Then, slowly, you can look for what you really want.
然后，慢慢地，你就可以寻找你真正想要的东西。
Look for a better one.
寻找一个更好的。
It sounds like you're offering me a job?
听起来你要给我一份工作？
You can work with me for a while to try it out.
你可以和我一起尝试一段时间。
Okay.
好的。
Then I'll give it a try.
那我就试试吧。
You might not last through it.
你可能无法坚持下去。
(Twenty thousand. Unavoidable. Wang Hao)
（两万。不可避免。王浩）
=Episode 20= (Rich)
=第20集=（丰富）
Rich, come here.
富贵，你过来吧。
See what I brought you.
看看我给你带来了什么。
Ham sausage. Do you want some?
火腿肠。你想要一些吗？
Can it eat this?
这个可以吃吗？
Of course.
当然。
I can feed it?
我可以喂它吗？
Rich, say thank you to her.
里奇，向她说声谢谢。
Here's ham sausage.
这是火腿肠。
Would you like to adopt Rich?
你想收养里奇吗？
Adopt?
采纳？
You don't want to keep it?
你不想保留它吗？
It's not that I don't want to.
并不是我不想。
My boyfriend is abroad year-round.
我男朋友常年在国外。
I'm going to join him next month.
下个月我要和他一起去。
So recently,
所以最近，
I've been trying to find a family to adopt it.
我一直在努力寻找一个家庭来收养它。
I haven't found a suitable one yet.
我还没有找到合适的。
I really can't take it with me.
我实在是带不走。
So,
所以，
if you could adopt it,
如果你能采纳的话
that would be perfect.
那将是完美的。
Rich,
富有的，
do you want to go home with me?
你想和我一起回家吗？
I've never had a dog before,
我以前没养过狗
but I can try.
但我可以尝试。
I think you can do it.
我认为你能做到。
Greet your godmother, Rich.
向你的教母问好，里奇。
- Hurry, thank godmother. - I am godmother now.
- 快点，谢谢教母。 - 我现在是教母了。
No.
不。
Sorry about that.
对此感到抱歉。
Rich.
富有的。
Shen Mo just bluntly told you
沉默只是直白的告诉你
he has heart disease and asked you not to leave him?
他有心脏病，叫你不要离开他？
Right, straight to the point, and very upfront.
不错，开门见山，非常直接。
Upfront?
预先？
He's shameless.
他真是无耻啊。
He admits he's shameless.
他承认自己无耻。
What kind of fate is this for me?
这对我来说是一种怎样的命运？
I just divorced a gambler.
我刚刚和一个赌徒离婚了。
Now here comes one with heart disease.
现在来了一位患有心脏病的人。
Should I accept him or not?
我该接受他还是不接受他？
If I accept him,
如果我接受他的话
I'm afraid I'll be trapped.
我担心我会被困住。
If I don't,
如果我不这样做，
I feel a bit sorry for him.
我觉得有点对不起他。
You definitely shouldn't.
你绝对不应该。
How old is he? Fifty? Sixty?
他几岁了？五十？六十？
Fifty-three.
五十三。
He's fifty-three,
他五十三岁了，
while you're barely thirty.
当你还不到三十岁的时候。
You should think it through.
你应该考虑清楚。
Will you serve an old man for the rest of your life?
你愿意侍奉一个老人一辈子吗？
I think you're right.
我认为你是对的。
I have my mom and kid.
我有我的妈妈和孩子。
I can't take on another old man.
我不能再接受另一个老人了。
Yes. I can't do that.
是的。我不能那样做。
Definitely not.
绝对不是。
You really need to think more about yourself.
你确实需要多为自己考虑一下。
Do you know that?
你知道吗？
I know.
我知道。
Take it out to go potty.
拿出来上厕所。
Come on.
快点。
Go potty now.
现在去上厕所吧。
I never expected you to have a dog.
我没想到你会养狗。
What about the dog when you do night rounds?
当你晚上巡查时，狗怎么办？
I just leave it at home when I do night rounds.
当我夜巡时，我就把它留在家里。
I installed a camera at home.
我在家里安装了一个摄像头。
If it's at home alone,
如果是一个人在家的话
I can check on it.
我可以检查一下。
It messes things up?
它把事情搞砸了？
It's very well-behaved.
它表现得非常好。
I feel like it has been trained before.
感觉之前就已经受过训练了。
How's that thing going for you?
那件事对你来说怎么样？
Has Barry calmed down?
巴里冷静了吗？
I'm not sure if he's still angry.
我不确定他是否还在生气。
He's probably doing better now.
他现在可能做得更好了。
Barry loves
巴里喜欢
showing off and building his image through charity work.
通过慈善工作来炫耀和树立自己的形象。
So I set up a Responsible Drinking Week for him.
所以我为他设立了负责任饮酒周。
I did it with media outlets,
我和媒体一起做了，
invited top influencers from various industries,
邀请各行业顶尖影响力人士，
and made him ambassador. He was thrilled.
并任命他为大使。他很激动。
Foreigners always buy it.
老外总是买。
I also invited Shen Mo as a distributor representative.
我还邀请了沉默作为经销商代表。
Is he coming?
他来了吗？
Of course! It's a great chance.
当然！这是一个很好的机会。
How could he miss it?
他怎么能错过呢？
He even took back all the returned wine today.
今天还把退回来的酒全都收回了。
Smart move! Killing two birds with one stone.
明智之举！一石二鸟。
All about people's will.
一切以民意为主。
But he's sick now, so he probably can't make it.
但他现在病了，所以他可能来不了了。
He'll likely send someone else.
他很可能会派其他人来。
(Drink Moderately, Live a Happy Life)
（适量饮酒，快乐生活）
It's a bit crooked.
有点歪了。
Hello.
你好。
(VIP Guest)
（贵宾）
(National Responsible Drinking Awareness Week, Drink Moderately, Live a Happy Life)
（全国负责任饮酒宣传周，适量饮酒，快乐生活）
(Gustav Sapet China)
（古斯塔夫·萨佩特中国）
Okay. First piece is Crescent Moon Quartet,
好的。第一个作品是《新月四重奏》，
- right? - Yes.
- 正确的？ - 是的。
Crescent Moon Quartet first.
月牙四重奏第一。
Then the second piece is
那么第二块就是
- Minuet, - Minuet.
- 小步舞曲， - 小步舞曲。
by Bach.
巴赫的。
Anything else?
还要别的吗？
Beethoven's Ode to Joy.
贝多芬的欢乐颂。
Keep the volume low.
保持低音量。
Keep it low.
保持低调。
It mustn't overpower.
它一定不能压倒一切。
Just keep it as background music.
只需将其保留为背景音乐即可。
- Okay. - Practiced already.
- 好的。 - 已经练习过了。
Wang Hao.
Wang Hao.
Ms. Zhao.
Ms. Zhao.
The truss counterweights are insufficient.
桁架配重不足。
With heavy winds today,
今天有大风，
what if the backdrop falls and hits someone?
如果背景掉下来砸到人怎么办？
Vendor's asking for scolding.
卖家要求骂人。
Don't bother scolding them.
不用费心去骂他们。
Tell them to buy cigarettes and give each worker a pack.
让他们去买烟，给每个工人一包。
Got it.
知道了。
Wait.
等待。
Tell the vendor.
告诉卖家。
If they won't even spend money
如果他们连钱都不肯花钱
on cigarettes,
在香烟上，
we won't spend money on their final payment.
我们不会在他们的最后付款上花钱。
Oh, right.
哦，对了。
Shen Mo's secretary called, saying he's not coming tonight.
沉默的秘书打来电话，说他今晚不来了。
He wouldn't say why when asked.
当被问及原因时，他不肯说。
I know why. Go ahead.
我知道为什么。前进。
- Grand and spectacular. - It is just a small event.
- 宏伟而壮观。 - 这只是一个小事件。
You are flattering me.
你这是在奉承我。
I saw the guest list.
我看到了宾客名单。
What small event gets so many big shots?
什么样的小事件能引来这么多大人物？
Well done.
干得好。
For charity, everyone pitches in willingly.
为了慈善事业，大家都心甘情愿地伸出援手。
(National Responsible Drinking Awareness Week, Drink Moderately, Live a Happy Life)
（全国负责任饮酒宣传周，适量饮酒，快乐生活）
Quite the scale today.
今天的规模相当。
Many company heads showed up.
不少公司负责人都到场了。
That's why I insisted you come, both professionally and personally.
这就是为什么我坚持让你来，无论是职业上还是个人上。
Your wife is over there.
你的妻子在那边。
If you don't need anything else,
如果你不需要别的东西的话
I'll attend to other matters.
其他事情我会处理。
Wait, hold on.
等等，坚持住。
Here's the thing.
事情是这样的。
I've been thinking.
我一直在想。
I was too harsh the other day.
那天我太严厉了。
Sorry, please don't take it to heart.
抱歉，请不要放在心上。
It's fine.
没关系。
I understand.
我明白。
You only snapped because you were stressed.
你只是因为压力大而发脾气。
- If it were me, I'd be angry too. - Thanks for understanding.
——如果是我，我也会生气。 - 感谢您的理解。
I can understand
我能理解
why you said I'm not qualified to be Sales Director.
为什么你说我没有资格当销售总监。
From the day I became a promoter,
从我成为推广员那天起，
I never felt any boss
我从来没有感受到任何老板
was fully qualified to be my superior.
完全有资格做我的上级。
Including Xu Yuntian.
Including Xu Yuntian.
So I can understand you.
所以我能理解你。
That's arrogant.
这就是傲慢。
Aggressive spirit in sales.
销售中的进取精神。
Mr. Fan.
范先生。
Zhao Mei.
Zhao Mei.
Long time no see.
好久不见。
Let me introduce.
我来介绍一下。
This is Dong Yue.
这是东岳。
This is the CEO of Ruijin Consulting,
这是瑞金咨询的CEO，
Mr. Fan.
范先生。
Hello.
你好。
Mr. Fan, nice to meet you.
范先生，很高兴认识您。
This is
这是
my husband.
我的丈夫。
Mr. Li, long time no see.
李先生，好久不见。
Have we met before?
我们以前见过吗？
That event last time.
上次那个活动。
Zhao Mei's event? I remember now.
赵梅事件？我现在想起来了。
It's Barry. He is here.
是巴里。他在这里。
Mr. Fan, let's go greet him.
范先生，我们去迎接一下吧。
Okay.
好的。
Come along?
一起来吗？
Liming Group and Jingchu Group
Liming Group and Jingchu Group
came because I begged several major clients.
来是因为我求了几个大客户。
Fan was going to Beijing
范要去北京
to meet a crucial client today. But I dragged him here.
今天去见一位重要客户。但我把他拖到了这里。
Barry.
巴里.
Let me introduce.
我来介绍一下。
This is Mr. Fan, CEO of Ruijin Consulting.
我是瑞金咨询首席执行官范先生。
Hello.
你好。
Thank you for strongly supporting our Responsible Drinking campaign.
感谢您大力支持我们的理性饮酒活动。
- It's the least we could do. - This is our head of HR, Ms. Qi.
- 这是我们至少能做的。 - 这是我们的人力资源主管，齐女士。
Mr. Fan, hello.
范先生，您好。
Hello.
你好。
This way.
这边走。
Actually, Dongming and I
其实我和东明
have always been your loyal users.
一直是您的忠实用户。
Barry,
巴里，
the guests at today's event are all heavyweight.
今天出席活动的嘉宾都是重量级人物。
It was all organized by my wife.
这一切都是我妻子安排的。
By the way,
顺便一提，
I heard Shen Mo is also coming today.
听说沉默今天也来了。
Very good.
非常好。
Please come this way for a photo.
请这边来拍照。
Barry,
巴里，
we'll go on stage to speak in five minutes.
五分钟后我们将上台发言。
Do you need to prepare?
你需要准备吗？
So soon? I'll quickly review it then.
这么快？那我会快速回顾一下。
Drink moderately.
适量饮酒。
Surprised?
惊讶吗？
A bit. How come you're here?
一点。你怎么在这里？
Because of your stupid event.
因为你的愚蠢事件。
I got up at 7:30 AM.
我早上 7:30 起床。
What was your company thinking?
你们公司是怎么想的？
A liquor company is promoting responsible drinking?
一家酒类公司正在提倡负责任的饮酒？
How hypocritical!
多么虚伪啊！
I actually think
我其实认为
if a liquor company promotes responsible drinking,
如果一家酒类公司提倡理性饮酒，
it will be more persuasive and educational.
它将更具说服力和教育意义。
That old man said the same thing.
那老者也说了同样的话。
He's furious about you kicking him aside
他对你把他踢到一边很生气
after using him,
使用他之后，
but he insisted I should come anyway, saying it's a separate matter.
但他坚持我无论如何都应该来，并说这是另一回事。
What happened? Why isn't Mr. Shen coming?
发生了什么？沉先生怎么没来？
He's sick.
他病了。
He said he wants me to be VP at the company.
他说他希望我担任公司的副总裁。
If I perform well,
如果我表现好的话
he'll leave me more money in his will.
他会在遗嘱中留给我更多的钱。
What illness? Is it serious?
什么病？严重吗？
Heart disease. I don't know if it's serious.
心脏病。不知道严重吗
Anyway, he's got many bad habits.
无论如何，他的坏习惯还是有很多的。
Him living this long is already a miracle.
他能活这么久，已经是一个奇迹了。
Let's not talk about him. Talk about you.
我们先不说他了。谈谈你。
Have you been secretly seeing other women behind my back?
你是不是背着我偷偷和别的女人约会了？
I'm seeing.
我看到了。
You're annoying! Why do you always upset me?
你真烦人！为什么你总是让我不高兴？
But no matter how you upset me, I still like you.
但无论你如何让我伤心，我仍然喜欢你。
Stop this.
停止这个。
Don't push.
别推。
People are watching.
人们正在观看。
We've broken up. Why are you doing this?
我们已经分手了。你为什么要这样做？
But I didn't agree.
但我没有同意。
You haven't told anyone, right?
你还没告诉过任何人吧？
I didn't tell anyone
我没有告诉任何人
because your dad told me
因为你爸爸告诉我
not to say anything for now.
暂时不说什么。
Excuses.
借口。
Is it him stopping you?
是他拦着你吗？
Or are you afraid of losing his support
或者你害怕失去他的支持
and reluctant to say it?
并且不愿意说出来？
Both.
两个都。
Why do I like you so much?
为什么我这么喜欢你？
What is it?
它是什么？
How wild!
多么狂野啊！
- What are you doing? - I am kissing my boyfriend.
- 你在干什么？ - 我正在亲吻我的男朋友。
What is that?
那是什么？
We'll take our seats.
我们就座。
It seems Shen Mo won't make it today.
看来沉默今天是来不了了。
That's Shen Mo's daughter.
那是沉默的女儿。
It looks like she is pursuing that guy.
看来她是在追求那个男​​人。
Salesmen in this field
该领域的销售人员
all have some tricks when dealing with women.
与女人打交道，都有一些技巧。
Alright, next, let's welcome with the warmest applause
好，接下来，让我们以最热烈的掌声欢迎
our advocate for responsible drinking on this occasion,
值此之际，我们倡导理性饮酒，
Barry, General Manager of Gustav Sapet China,
Barry，古斯塔夫萨佩特中国区总经理，
to come on stage and deliver a speech for us.
上台为我们发表演讲。
- My turn now. - Please give him a round of applause.
- 现在轮到我了。 - 请给他热烈的掌声。
First, I want to thank you all
首先，我要感谢大家
for coming to our Responsible Drinking event.
感谢您参加我们的负责任饮酒活动。
As the Chinese often say,
正如中国人常说的，
a gentleman needs to be slightly drunk when drinking alcohol.
君子饮酒须微醉。
True grace lies in knowing when to advance or retreat.
真正的恩典在于知道何时进或退。
I'm very happy for this opportunity
我很高兴有这个机会
to meet all of you guys,
为了和大家见面，
my partners.
我的伙伴们。
I'm very thrilled for the opportunity I have here.
我对在这里拥有的机会感到非常兴奋。
We all have here.
我们这里都有。
I love you. I can't be without you.
我爱你。我不能没有你。
(When Shen Xing hugged me,)
（当沈星拥抱我的时候，）
(I suddenly realized)
（我突然意识到）
(that although she's crazy, she's actually not stupid at all.)
（虽然她疯了，但她其实一点也不傻。）
(All her questions cut right to the heart of the issue.)
（她所有的问题都切中了问题的核心。）
(For example, she knows that on occasions like today,)
（例如，她知道像今天这样的场合，）
(I would never let her be too embarrassed.)
（我永远不会让她太尴尬。）
(If even drinking requires rationality, how could I not be rational?)
（如果连喝酒都需要理性，我怎么可能不理性呢？）
This event is really good.
这个活动真是太好了。
I bet headquarters will absolutely love this event.
我敢打赌总部绝对会喜欢这个活动。
Zhao Mei is indeed a very smart person.
赵梅确实是一个非常聪明的人。
She knows how to make me happy,
她知道如何让我开心
although she spent quite a bit this time.
虽然她这次花费了不少。
What's wrong?
怎么了？
Internal Audit Department sent an email.
内审部发来邮件。
It says one of our suppliers claimed
据说我们的一位供应商声称
that during their internal investigation,
在内部调查期间，
they discovered their employee bribed Zhao Mei.
他们发现他们的员工贿赂了赵梅。
How much was the bribe?
受贿金额是多少？
They attached an invoice worth 20,000 yuan.
他们附上了一张价值2万元的发票。
It's from a pet store.
这是从宠物店买的。
A pet store?
宠物店？
Are you kidding me?
你在开玩笑吧？
(Invoice Notification)
（发票通知）
When Tengyue Media's people were doing internal review,
腾跃传媒的人在做内审的时候，
they found this invoice worth 20,000 yuan from pet store.
他们从宠物店找到了这张价值2万元的发票。
The reason they reported internally
他们内部举报的原因
was that this asset was given to you as a gift.
是这个资产是作为礼物送给你的。
Tengyue Media?
腾跃传媒？
The head of Tengyue Media and I
我和腾跃传媒负责人
only met once at a bidding meeting.
只在投标会议上见过一次面。
I seldom talked to him.
我很少和他说话。
I don't even have his WeChat.
我连他的微信都没有。
How could I have accepted his gift?
我怎么可能接受他的礼物呢？
The person who contacted you was Tengyue Media's Senior Manager,
联系你的人是腾跃传媒的高级经理，
Lu Ting.
Lu Ting.
Lu Ting?
Lu Ting?
I don't know this person. I have never heard of her.
我不认识这个人。我从未听说过她。
Call her over. I can confront her.
把她叫过来。我可以面对她。
She has already resigned.
她已经辞职了。
Then this is utterly ridiculous.
那么这真是太荒谬了。
You're questioning me based solely
你只是单纯地质疑我
on notes left by someone
在某人留下的笔记上
who resigned and an invoice?
谁辞职了，有发票吗？
And do you even know
你知道吗
that Tengyue Media
那腾跃传媒
is no longer our supplier?
不再是我们的供应商？
Last week, during the bidding
上周，在招标期间
for the Spring Festival promotion, they didn't win the bid.
春节促销，他们没有中标。
We are aware of that.
我们知道这一点。
However, they specifically informed us,
然而，他们特别告诉我们，
so we have to look into it.
所以我们必须调查一下。
Okay.
好的。
Let me say this again.
让我再说一遍。
I do not know Lu Ting.
我不认识陆婷。
I have not accepted anything
我还没有接受任何东西
from this person or this company.
来自此人或这家公司。
What you're asking me about now is completely baseless.
你现在问我的话完全是毫无根据的。
Then, have you received anything
那你有收到什么东西吗
related to pets recently?
最近和宠物有关吗？
Pets?
宠物？
A colleague saw
有同事看到
you posted a dog on Moments this morning.
今天早上你在朋友圈发了一条狗。
According to company policy,
根据公司政策，
accepting assets worth more than 5,000 yuan from suppliers
接受供应商价值5000元以上资产
is considered bribery.
被视为贿赂。
Zhao Mei, you must think very carefully about this.
赵梅，你一定要好好考虑一下。
(Zhao Mei) (Hello, are you there?)
（赵梅）（喂，在吗？）
(Message sent, but rejected by the recipient)
（消息已发送，但被收件人拒绝）
(My boyfriend is abroad year-round.)
（我男朋友常年在国外。）
(I'm joining him next month.)
（我下个月要加入他。）
(So recently,)
（所以最近，）
(I've been trying to find a family to adopt it.)
（我一直在努力寻找一个家庭来收养它。）
(I haven't found a suitable one yet.)
（我还没找到合适的。）
(I really can't take it with me.)
（我真的带不走。）
(Lu Ting) (So, if you could adopt him,)
（陆霆）（所以，如果你可以收养他的话，）
(that would be perfect.)
（那就完美了。）
Ms. Zhao.
Ms. Zhao.
Do you know this person?
你认识这个人吗？
I know her. She is Lu Ting.
我认识她。她就是陆婷。
We worked together on events. She's from Tengyue Media.
我们在活动中合作。她是腾跃传媒的。
But she probably resigned last month.
但她可能上个月辞职了。
Do you have her contact information?
你有她的联系方式吗？
Yeah.
是的。
What? Should I call her?
什么？我应该给她打电话吗？
Call her.
打电话给她。
The subscriber you dialed cannot be connected.
您拨打的用户无法连接。
Please redial later.
请稍后重拨。
Strange.
奇怪的。
Let me send her a message.
让我给她发个消息。
She blocked me.
她屏蔽了我。
Expected.
预期的。
What happened?
发生了什么？
Before resigning, Lu Ting
陆婷辞职前
submitted an invoice worth 20,000 yuan to their company,
向其公司提交了价值2万元的发票，
saying she gave me something.
说她给了我东西。
So their company specifically informed our internal audit team.
所以他们公司专门通知了我们内审团队。
I don't understand.
我不明白。
They said I accepted a gift.
他们说我接受了一份礼物。
Did you accept it?
你接受了吗？
No!
不！
I did.
我做到了。
But I genuinely didn't know it was meant to frame me.
但我真的不知道这是为了陷害我。
I got set up.
我已经安排好了。
That wretch.
那个坏蛋。
What do we do now?
我们现在做什么？
Find Lu Ting and return the thing to her.
找到陆婷，把东西还给她。
Then catch the mastermind behind this.
然后抓住这件事的幕后主使。
Otherwise...
否则...
Otherwise what?
否则怎么办？
Do you know our company has a policy?
你知道我们公司有政策吗？
Accepting gifts worth over 5,000 yuan
接受价值5000元以上的礼品
from suppliers counts as bribery.
来自供应商的行为视为贿赂。
I didn't know that.
我不知道。
At worst,
最坏的情况是，
the company could fire me anytime now,
公司随时可以解雇我
without paying me any compensation.
不给我任何补偿。
At best,
充其量，
this is a financial issue.
这是一个财务问题。
They most likely won't promote me.
他们很可能不会提升我。
I'll go find Lu Ting right now and get to the bottom of this.
我现在就去找陆廷，查个水落石出。
Ms. Zhao, can I ask
赵小姐，请问可以吗？
what you actually accepted?
你实际上接受了什么？
A dog.
一只狗。
Shoot.
射击。
Here.
这里。
- Amazing. - Here.
- 惊人的。 - 这里。
Pet store invoice?
宠物店发票？
For how much?
多少钱？
20,000 yuan.
2万元。
20,000 yuan?
两万元？
For 20,000 yuan, the internal audit team is investigating?
2万元，内审组调查？
Don't think 20,000 yuan is a small amount.
别以为两万元是小数目。
Many people have that misconception.
很多人都有这样的误解。
Accepting gifts over 5,000 yuan counts as bribery.
收受礼物金额超过5000元的，属于行贿罪。
So, you think Zhao Mei is innocent?
那么，你认为赵梅是无辜的吗？
I don't know if she's innocent or not.
我不知道她是否无辜。
But from what I know, she doesn't have a pet.
但据我所知，她没有养宠物。
She does! Didn't you see her posts?
她做到了！你没看到她的帖子吗？
I seldom checked posts.
我很少查帖子。
It's already deleted.
已经删除了。
But I have it here.
但我这里有。
Look.
看。
Qi Youlan sent it to me and asked for my handling opinion.
齐友兰发给我，征求我的处理意见。
So, what's your opinion?
那么，你有什么看法呢？
My opinion is simple. Financial issue is a red line.
我的意见很简单。财务问题是一条红线。
Since the supplier reported it, we definitely have to investigate.
既然供应商举报了，我们肯定要调查。
Because the amount isn't that large,
因为金额不是很大，
we might not necessarily ask her to resign.
我们不一定要求她辞职。
But she definitely won't get the Sales Director position.
但她绝对不会得到销售总监的职位。
So that's the real goal, right?
所以这才是真正的目标，对吧？
To stop her promotion.
阻止她升职。
It is obvious.
这是显而易见的。
But won't everyone think I'm the one who set this up?
但大家会不会认为这是我安排的呢？
Aren't you?
你不是吗？
(Moss Cafe) Then this person
（Moss Cafe）然后这个人
knows your company's policies way too well.
对你们公司的政策太了解了。
Very familiar.
很熟悉。
Could it be someone from your company?
会不会是你们公司的人？
Think about it.
想一想。
If Zhao Mei gets into trouble,
如果赵梅遇到麻烦，
who will benefit the most?
谁将受益最大？
Definitely Dong Yue. No need to think.
肯定是东岳。无需思考。
Your promotion fails for bribery.
您的晋升因贿赂而失败。
He's the one who benefits the most.
他才是受益最大的人。
But I really don't think it's him.
但我真的不认为是他。
Back then, you thought
那时你以为
Li Dongming was a good guy rising above the filth.
李东明是一个出身于污秽之中的好人。
Think about it.
想一想。
So what are you going to do now?
那么你现在要做什么？
Do you want to be the hero saving the damsel?
你想成为拯救少女的英雄吗？
Or throw stones while she's down?
或者当她情绪低落时扔石头？
Both.
两个都。
Really, your imagination is just too vivid.
真的，你的想象力太丰富了。
Do you think someone might be trying to help you?
您认为有人可能会试图帮助您吗？
(I heard about your issue.)
（我听说了你的问题。）
(Dong Yue) (Do you have a photo of the dog giver?)
（冬月）（有送狗人的照片吗？）
(Yes.)
（是的。）
(Zhao Mei)
(Zhao Mei)
Boss.
老板。
Is your friend who helped find the one I wanted
你的朋友帮我找到了我想要的人吗
last time still there?
上次还在吗？
I need his help again.
我再次需要他的帮助。
She should be easy to find. She is in our circle too.
她应该很容易找到。她也在我们圈子里。
Mr. Li.
先生。李。
You guys go ahead. I...
你们继续吧。我...
I left my phone at the restaurant.
我把手机落在餐厅了。
You go ahead.
你继续吧。
(Shan Yunfei) (Did you see what she bought?)
（单云飞）（你看到她买了什么吗？）
(Wang Xiaomi) (She's drinking Brain Blast again.)
（王小米）（又喝Brain Blast了。）
(How many bottles has she had today?)
（她今天喝了多少瓶？）
(Shan Yunfei) (She just bought many more.)
（单云飞）（她刚买了很多。）
(Chen Mina) (It shouldn't be drunk too much, right?)
（陈米娜）（应该不会喝太多吧？）
(Wang Xiaomi) (Too tired. No choice.)
（王小米）（太累了，没办法。）
(She has to work overtime.)
（她必须加班。）
(Wang Anran) (Who doesn't work overtime?)
（王安然）（谁不加班？）
(Wang Xiaomi) (It is nothing like ours.)
（王小米）（和我们的一点都不一样。）
(We do one kind of job.)
（我们做一种工作。）
(But her?)
（但是她呢？）
(She does one kind of job during the day and another at night,)
（她白天做一种工作，晚上做另一种工作，）
(Chatter Squad) (and still works past midnight.)
（Chatter Squad）（午夜过后仍然工作。）
(Shan Yunfei) (The 108 methods of working overtime.)
（单云飞）（加班的108种方法。）
Don't chat idly during work hours.
工作时间不要闲聊。
Meeting in Conference Room 3 in ten minutes.
十分钟后在 3 号会议室开会。
- Yes. - Okay.
- 是的。 - 好的。
How does he know we're chatting?
他怎么知道我们在聊天？
No idea.
不知道。
Any spyware on our computers?
我们的计算机上有间谍软件吗？
It can't be right.
这不可能是对的。
Why is Xiao so mean lately?
肖最近怎么这么凶？
The post-illness good days ended that fast?
病后的好日子就这么快结束了吗？
He's anxious.
他很着急。
The Shannan project
山南项目
got cut short as the client ran out of money.
由于客户没钱了，所以时间被缩短了。
The CVS project isn't still signed.
CVS 项目尚未签署。
Next year's KPIs
明年的 KPI
won't be met.
不会被满足。
Does that mean more layoffs?
这是否意味着更多裁员？
Hard to tell.
很难说。
(Risk Prevention and Response Strategy) Regarding the problems and challenges,
（风险防范与应对策略）针对存在的问题和挑战，
we took countermeasures.
我们采取了对策。
Therefore, we must proactively prevent potential risks
因此，我们必须主动防范潜在风险
and implement preventative measures.
并落实预防措施。
That concludes my summary. Thank you.
我的总结到此结束。谢谢。
Good.
好的。
Next. Who's next, Xiaomi?
下一个。下一个是谁，小米？
Qiao Hailun, you're up.
Qiao Hailun, you're up.
MT Company was not very satisfied with the analysis and conclusions
MT公司对分析结论并不满意
we provided
我们提供了
(Contents) in the last phase.
（内容）在最后阶段。
The main issues are concentrated in three areas.
主要问题集中在三个方面。
Competitor analysis, response strategies, and team building.
竞争对手分析、应对策略和团队建设。
First, competitor analysis.
首先，竞争对手分析。
Oh my!
天啊！
What is that sound?
那是什么声音？
It's a cat meowing.
这是一只猫在喵喵叫。
It's in heat.
正处于热状态。
Why that sound on her computer?
为什么她的电脑上有这个声音？
What's going on?
这是怎么回事？
This is crazy.
这太疯狂了。
No, it's...
不，这是...
Fix it, hurry!
赶紧修吧！
I...
我...
Well...
出色地...
How can you be so stupid?
你怎么可以这么蠢呢？
How did you even get hired with your IQ?
以你的智商，你是怎么被录用的？
I... Wait...
我……等等……
Can you fix it or not?
你能修好还是不能修好？
How long did MT Company give you for the preliminary work?
MT公司给了你们多长时间的前期工作？
Still not satisfied?
还是不满意？
If you can't do it,
如果你做不到的话
let someone else handle it.
让别人来处理。
Stop wasting time here.
别再在这里浪费时间了。
You're wasting everyone's time in this room.
你在浪费这个房间里每个人的时间。
I...
我...
Alright, enough.
好吧，够了。
Xiaomi.
小米。
You'll take over
你将接管
this project.
这个项目。
Got it!
知道了！
Why are you waiting?
你为什么等？
To improve product quality and taste,
为提高产品品质和口感，
MT Company continuously optimizes its product formulations
MT公司不断优化产品配方
to meet consumer demands.
以满足消费者的需求。
I didn't know the woman who gave me the dog
我不认识送我狗的女人
is named Lu Ting.
名叫陆婷。
I always thought she was just a regular running buddy.
我一直以为她只是一个普通的跑步伙伴。
She said she was going abroad and couldn't take the dog.
她说她要出国，不能带狗。
She asked if I can keep it.
她问我是否可以保留它。
I said yes.
我说是的。
That's it.
就是这样。
So you did accept that dog.
所以你确实接受了那只狗。
I accepted it, but it wasn't a bribe.
我接受了，但这不是贿赂。
I was helping her take care of it, do you understand?
我是在帮她处理这件事，你明白吗？
There's a fundamental difference here.
这里有一个根本的区别。
I was set up.
我被陷害了。
But you can't prove that.
但你无法证明这一点。
Based on the evidence we have,
根据我们掌握的证据，
you did accept something
你确实接受了一些东西
worth 20,000 yuan.
价值2万元。
And it came directly from our supplier.
它直接来自我们的供应商。
I didn't know she was a supplier.
我不知道她是供应商。
What do I have to say to make you believe me?
我要说什么才能让你相信我？
I've worked at GST for ten years.
我在 GST 工作了十年。
I wouldn't
我不会
stoop so low as to covet a dog, right?
弯得低得连狗都贪图吧？
It's not like it's an apartment.
这不像是公寓。
Just kidding. Don't write it down.
只是在开玩笑。不要写下来。
I was talking nonsense. Don't record it.
我是在胡说八道。不要记录它。
Zhao Mei,
Zhao Mei,
stay calm.
保持冷静。
We're not enemies.
我们不是敌人。
No, I...
不，我...
I just
我只是
truly feel like you're completely
真正感觉你完全
interrogating me as a suspect.
把我当作嫌疑人审问。
Okay.
好的。
Ms. Qi wants to see you.
齐女士想见你。
(Qi Youlan)
(Qi Youlan)
Come in.
进来。
Have a seat.
请坐。
Regarding the report filed against you,
关于针对您提出的报告，
I've discussed it with higher-ups
我已经和高层商量过了
and gathered their input.
并收集他们的意见。
First,
第一的，
you did violate company policy.
你确实违反了公司政策。
But the amount involved was minor.
但涉案金额较小。
Additionally,
此外，
higher-ups highly values
高层高度重视
your contributions to the company.
您对公司的贡献。
So we won't treat this as bribery.
所以我们不会将其视为贿赂。
There's a 'but' coming, isn't there?
有个“但是”来了，不是吗？
But we can't proceed with your promotion at this time.
但我们目前无法继续您的促销活动。
I don't accept this.
我不接受这个。
I was framed.
我被陷害了。
I refuse to accept it. Absolutely not!
我拒绝接受。绝对不是！
Seems Ms. Zhao's bribery accusation
看来赵女士涉嫌受贿
won't be cleared soon.
不会很快被清除。
What bribery?
什么贿赂？
She didn't take bribes.
她没有受贿。
I was just speculating.
我只是猜测。
Everyone's saying it, right?
大家都这么说吧？
The more people say it,
说的人越多，
the less you should say it.
你越不应该说。
Hao,
浩，
do you truly believe she didn't accept that dog?
你真的相信她不接受那只狗吗？
No.
不。
Actually, I think she did take it.
事实上，我认为她确实接受了。
But she didn't view it as a bribe.
但她并不认为这是贿赂。
She thought it was a dog and never expected such consequences.
她以为那是一只狗，没想到会造成这样的后果。
What are you implying?
你在暗示什么？
I'm not implying anything.
我并不是在暗示什么。
I'm just stating facts.
我只是陈述事实。
Don't get defensive.
不要采取防御措施。
Whether it's true or not, Ms. Zhao has taken a major fall this time.
不管真假，赵女士这次摔了大跤。
And it's dragging our whole department down.
这拖累了我们整个部门。
I heard internal audit team plans
我听说内部审计团队的计划
to investigate our department again.
再次调查我们部门。
Really?
真的吗？
That's brutal.
这太残酷了。
When elephants fight, the grass gets trampled.
当大象打架时，草地会被践踏。
Enough. Just pipe down.
足够的。只需向下管道即可。
Hey, Miss. All alone?
嘿，小姐，一个人吗？
Drowning yourself?
自己淹死吗？
Feeling upset?
感到不安吗？
Drank too much? Let me take you home.
喝太多了？让我带你回家。
Don't touch me!
别碰我！
Do you even know where she lives?
你甚至知道她住在哪里吗？
She's my girl. None of your business.
她是我的女孩。关你屁事。
And I'm your mother!
我是你的妈妈！
What's her name?
她叫什么名字？
Get lost!
迷路！
Too young to be acting this way.
太年轻了，不能做出这样的举动。
Danning, you're here.
丹宁，你来了。
How'd you get this messed up?
你怎么把这事搞砸了？
Let's go home.
我们回家吧。
Where to?
去哪儿？
Anywhere. Just move.
任何地方。只要移动。
Grab the wine.
拿起酒来。
The wine.
酒。
Black Knight? Drinking the competitor's wine now?
黑骑士？现在喝竞争对手的酒吗？
Check out this view.
看看这个视图。
Paired with this excellent wine.
搭配这款优质葡萄酒。
This wine, let me tell you,
这酒，让我告诉你，
I've always wanted to try it.
我一直想尝试一下。
It's exceptional.
这很特别。
Let me taste it.
让我尝尝。
Honestly, it's laughable.
老实说，这很可笑。
All because
都是因为
of a dog...
一只狗的...
I was ruined by a dog.
我被一只狗毁了。
I heard
我听说
someone once said
有人曾经说过
that in a company,
就是在一个公司里，
if promotions came solely through hard work,
如果晋升完全是通过努力工作，
that company must be worthless.
那家公司肯定一文不值。
That was Li Dongming, right?
那是李东明吧？
Exactly.
确切地。
Today, I finally understand completely.
今天我终于彻底明白了。
I don't have that kind of luck.
我没有这样的运气。
Don't talk nonsense.
别乱说。
It's true.
这是真的。
Really, the more I think about it,
确实，我越想越觉得，
the more I feel I'm not destined for this.
我越觉得我不是命中注定的。
What's the point of me trying so hard?
我这么努力有什么意义？
I'm sorry, Danning.
对不起，丹宁。
I must have disappointed you.
我一定让你失望了。
What are you saying?
你在说什么？
Aren't we just employees?
我们不只是员工吗？
Is it really that serious?
事情真的有那么严重吗？
I'm deeply disappointed in myself.
我对自己深感失望。
Just be happy.
只要快乐就好。
What's to be disappointed about?
有什么可失望的呢？
(Gustav Sapet China)
（古斯塔夫·萨佩特中国）
I want to see Ms. Qi.
我想见齐小姐。
Stop making a fuss.
别再闹了。
I admit it.
我承认。
You accepted reality so quickly?
这么快就接受现实了？
What else can I do?
我还能做什么？
This whole thing is clearly a setup.
这整件事显然是一个安排。
The boss and my colleagues know it.
老板和同事都知道。
But rules are rules.
但规则就是规则。
I did violate the rules.
我确实违反了规则。
So I'll accept it.
所以我会接受它。
But you can also view this matter
不过你也可以查看这个事情
from a positive perspective.
从积极的角度来看。
When someone climbs higher in status,
当一个人的地位上升时，
they encounter absurd situations.
他们遇到了荒谬的情况。
Let me make an inappropriate analogy.
让我打一个不恰当的比喻。
Like when Xu Yuntian encountered the sales lady,
就像徐云天遇到售货小姐时，
and you met that dog.
你遇见了那只狗。
It proves your life is on the rise.
这证明你的生活正在上升。
You're blocking someone's path.
你挡住了别人的路。
So they meticulously plot against you.
所以他们精心策划针对你。
Conversely, if you remained at a very low level,
相反，如果你保持在很低的水平，
who would target an ordinary sales lady?
谁会瞄准一个普通的销售女士？
She'd never face such things, right?
她绝对不会遇到这样的事情吧？
Thanks for comforting me.
谢谢你安慰我。
Okay, got it. Thanks.
好的，明白了。谢谢。
Does Wang Hao like you secretly?
王浩偷偷喜欢你吗？
He told the internal audit team
他告诉内部审计团队
that the 20,000-yuan dog
那只2万元的狗
was a gift from Tengyue Media for him.
是腾跃传媒送给他的礼物。
He fostered it with you, and you were unaware.
他和你一起培养它，而你却浑然不觉。
What?
什么？
I'll find him and stop him.
我会找到他并阻止他。
Are you crazy?
你疯了？
Wang Hao never accepted bribes.
王浩从不收受贿赂。
He's lying.
他在撒谎。
He's saving you.
他正在拯救你。
Do I not know
难道我不知道吗
he's doing this for you?
他这样做是为了你吗？
I've already confessed. I don't need him to cover for me.
我已经表白了。我不需要他来替我掩护。
Honestly, I shouldn't say this.
老实说，我不应该说这个。
But since I really can't find
但由于我实在找不到
a better person than you to lead the promoters,
一个比你更好的人来领导发起人，
please accept Wang Hao's goodwill.
请接受王浩的善意。
What I can do is
我能做的是
to ensure he leaves with full dignity.
确保他有尊严地离开。
I won't accept his kindness.
我不会接受他的好意。
I refuse to let my people take the fall for me.
我拒绝让我的人民为我承担责任。
Where's Wang Hao?
王浩在哪儿？
I haven't seen him. Did he come today?
我没见过他。他今天来了吗？
He hasn't replied to my morning text.
他还没有回复我早上的短信。
Should I call him again?
我应该再给他打电话吗？
There's something else I need to tell you.
我还有件事要告诉你。
Fang said she's going home.
方说她要回家了。
- We're all persuading her. She... - Wait.
- 我们都在说服她。她... - 等等。
Wait a second.
等一下。
(Resignation Letter of Wang Hao)
（王浩辞职信）
(Dong Yue is appointed as Gustav Sapet China Sales Director)
（董岳被任命为Gustav Sapet中国区销售总监）
(Now Dong Yue is appointed)
（现任命董岳）
(as Gustav Sapet China Sales Director.)
（担任 Gustav Sapet 中国销售总监。）
(I suddenly remembered a saying.)
（突然想起一句话。）
(Pure white expanse that is utterly clean.)
（纯白广阔，清净无染。）
(After all that work, I ended up where I started.)
（完成所有这些工作后，我最终回到了开始的地方。）
(Li Dongming said I need his help.)
（李东明说我需要他的帮助。）
(Dong Yue said I'm unqualified to be Sales Director.)
（冬越说我没有资格当销售总监。）
(What they said)
（他们说的话）
(makes perfect sense.)
（很有道理。）
♪All the stars are out tonight♪
♪今晚所有明星都出来了♪
♪Too much of shame♪
♪太羞耻了♪
♪To waste it crying♪
♪浪费时间哭泣♪
♪Leave all behind you♪
♪把一切都抛在身后♪
♪Gotta go on to better things♪
♪一定要继续做更好的事情♪
♪You know how far you've gone♪
♪你知道你已经走了多远♪
♪In the fire you rise again♪
♪在烈火中你再次崛起♪
♪You made it through the worst♪
♪你已经度过了最艰难的时期♪
♪The best is yet to come♪
♪最好的尚未到来♪
♪Isn't it magical♪
♪是不是很神奇♪
♪Listen, look, how beautiful the night is♪
♪听，看，夜晚多美丽♪
♪With countless lights on, is someone heartbroken again♪
♪无数灯亮，又有人心碎♪
♪The sound of a heart shattering on the ground is so crisp♪
♪心脏摔在地上的声音多么清脆♪
♪Turn on a light. A lonely heart needs comfort♪
♪打开灯。孤独的心需要安慰♪
♪Sweat, toil, dawn, dusk♪
♪汗水、辛劳、黎明、黄昏♪
♪Devaluing self-respect just for some hot food♪
♪为了一些热食而贬低自尊♪
♪But I don't want to♪
♪但我不想♪
♪Sell dignity at a price, trampling on past vows♪
♪以代价出卖尊严，践踏过去的誓言♪
♪Until 3 AM♪
♪直到凌晨3点♪
♪Locking dreams away in a drawer♪
♪把梦想锁在抽屉里♪
♪Just to earn some meager profit♪
♪只是为了赚取微薄的利润♪
♪No matter how hard I try, it only brings sobs♪
♪无论我如何努力，都只会带来抽泣♪
♪Renewing yearly, gone with no return, teetering, utterly bland♪
♪年复一年，一去不复返，摇摇欲坠，平淡无奇♪
♪Leave all behind you♪
♪把一切都抛在身后♪
♪Gotta go on to better things♪
♪一定要继续做更好的事情♪
♪You know how far you've gone♪
♪你知道你已经走了多远♪
♪In the fire you rise again♪
♪在烈火中你再次崛起♪
♪You made it through the worst♪
♪你已经度过了最艰难的时期♪
♪The best is yet to come♪
♪最好的尚未到来♪
♪Isn't it magical♪
♪是不是很神奇♪
♪All the stars are out tonight♪
♪今晚所有明星都出来了♪
♪And I see them sparkling♪
♪我看到它们闪闪发光♪
♪Nobody knows♪
♪没人知道♪
♪What tomorrow brings♪
♪明天会发生什么♪
♪You made it through the worst♪
♪你已经度过了最艰难的时期♪
♪The best is yet to come♪
♪最好的尚未到来♪
♪Isn't it magical♪
♪是不是很神奇♪
♪Feeling uneasy, yet no one's chasing me♪
♪心里不安，却没人追我♪
♪Retreating step by step, everything turning to ash♪
♪步步后退，一切化为灰烬♪
♪I'm silent, I'm roaring♪
♪我沉默，我咆哮♪
♪This helplessness keeps pushing me towards the cliff♪
♪这种无助不断将我推向悬崖♪
♪Trembling legs carry away a shattered soul♪
♪颤抖的双腿带走了破碎的灵魂♪
♪Who wants to be just a passerby♪
♪谁愿意只是一个路人♪
♪Isn't it magical♪
♪是不是很神奇♪